Anne Henrietta Martin Papers BANC MSS P-G 282
The Bancroft Library
- Correspondence, 1892-1951; box 1-19
  - Campaign Correspondence, 1920; Sub-Series 3; Boxes 17-19
    - Collier's Magazine, April-June 1920 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      2 letters. Signed by Loren Palmer, concerning an article on her campaign.
    - Collins, Steve, September-November 1920; 4 letters (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Coonley, Queen Ferry, April-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - D (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Davis, Emily, April-July 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Day, Katharine B., September-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Dunston, Wearn, September-November 1920; 6 letters (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - E (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Evans, Elizabeth G., May 9-18, 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - F (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Finnegan, Lilian M., 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Flannigan, Minnie, July 14-30, 1920; 4 letters (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Foote, Mrs. Cora, June-July 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Francis, Philip, February-April 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - G (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Gibbons, O.J., October-November 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Goldwater, France, July-August 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Granville-Smith, Jessica, July 9, 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Greeley, Helen Hay, May-November 1920; 17 letters (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Grock, Nellie H., May-June 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - H (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Hamar, Thomas, August-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Hamilton, S.H., September-November 1920; 4 letters (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Hatch, Jane, September-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Hayes, Thomas H., October-November 1920; 3 letters (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Hazard, Mrs. F.R., May-September 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Hendel, Helen, 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Hendrickson, Mrs. A.H., October 1-18, 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Hill, William, September-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Hopkins, J.A.H., April-June 1920 (Box 17, Folder 51)
      8 letters. Mostly as Chairman of the "Committee of 48."
    - Howard, Edith, July 9-13, 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Howard, Elbert, April-November 1920; 7 letters (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - I (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, May-June 1920 (Box 17, Folder 55)
      2 letters. Endorsing Anne Martin as senatorial candidate.
    - J (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Jameison, Alex, April-September 1920; 8 letters (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Jewett, J.S., October-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - K (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Karavs, Pearl, June-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Kent, Elizabeth, March-December 1920; 12 letters (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Kenyon, Sophie T., October-November 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Kerr, Lillian H., May-June 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Kuchenmeister, Mrs. K., June-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - L (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Lapeen, Mrs. J., October-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Leilich, Elizabeth, November 2-3, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Lincoln, Kathryn, May-July 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Lloyd, Charles E., September-November 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Joseph, Dr. T.B., October-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Long, Margaret, May-October 1920; 24 letters (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - M (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - McClure, William, June 15-29, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - McCutcheon, Lila, April-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - MacFarlane, Helen I, July-November 1920; 10 letters (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - MacHenry, November 3, 1920; 2 telegrams (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Marsh, Mabel, June-July 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Martin, Mrs. W.O., 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - May, Marion, April-June 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Morehouse, H.V., May 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Mullen, Katharine, June-October 1920; 7 letters (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - N (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Katzenstein, Caroline, June-August 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - The Nation, April-November 1920 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      3 letters. One signed by Oswald Garrison Villard
    - Neilson, Francis, June 1-16, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Nevada Secretary of State, August-November 1920 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      3 letters. Signed by George Bradigan
    - O (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Oastler, H.C., October 7-29, 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Olsen, Charles W., September-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Ostrum, Ida May, April-July 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - P (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Parratt, Edna Martin, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Pope, Robert Anderson, May 14-20, 1920; 4 letters (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - R (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Ross, Margery, July 6-7, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Ross, Mrs. William, July-November 1920; 5 letters (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - S (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Sain, C.M., May-August 1920; 4 letters (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Sanford, Frank H., August-November 1920; 6 letters (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Savage, R.E., October 22-29, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Schold, Martha, September-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Scholfield, Sara Jane, July 23-28, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Simpson, Ingeborg, June-November 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Staab, Henry G., October 22-November 14, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Steere, Cora E., June 18-28, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - T (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - U (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - V (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Vernon, Mabel, July-October 1920; 3 telegrams (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Vernon, Tom, October-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Vose, Julia J., June-July 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - W (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Whittemore, Margaret, September-October 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Whorton, George L., June-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Wilkinson, Bertha, October 21-26, 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Winnemucca Volunteer Fire Department, August 2-24, 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Winter, Helen Clegg, May-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Withers, T.L., July-August 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Wold, Emma, September-November 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Wood, John H., July-October 1920; 3 letters (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - The World, April-October 1920; 2 letters (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Y (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Z (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - unsigned letters (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Outgoing correspondence, April -November 1920 (Box 19, Folder 1-9)
- General Papers, 1867-1951; Carton 1-8; Carton 9, folders 1-42
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Includes writings by Martin and others, campaign materials, files on various organizations (which include minutes, newsletters and correspondence), drafts of correspondence and subject files. Large groups of like materials have been further organized into the following sub-groups: Articles by others; Campaign materials; Legislative; Newspaper clippings; Organizations; Serials; and Writings
  - Articles by various authors, 1867-1951
    - Romanzo Adams, 1867-1948 (Carton 1, Folder 1)
    - Jane Addams, 1916 (Carton 1, Folder 2)
    - John B. Andrews, 1916-1917 (Carton 1, Folder 3)
    - [?] Atkinson, 1914 (Carton 1, Folder 4)
    - Mary Austin, 1922 (Carton 1, Folder 5)
    - Mary Beard and Florence Kelley, 1914-1916 (Carton 1, Folder 6)
    - Alice Stone Blackwell (Carton 1, Folder 7)
    - Elizabeth Baker Bohan (Carton 1, Folder 8)
    - William E. Borah, 1917 (Carton 1, Folder 9)
    - Sara Sibree Bornemann (Carton 1, Folder 10)
    - Borden Parker Bowne, 1910 (Carton 1, Folder 11)
    - Josephine E. Butler (Carton 1, Folder 12)
    - Ida Clyde Clarke, 1922 (Carton 1, Folder 13)
    - Laura Clay (Carton 1, Folder 14)
    - Winnifred Harper Cooley, 1918 (Carton 1, Folder 15)
    - Caroline Bartlett Crane (Carton 1, Folder 16)
    - Sarah H. Dorris (Carton 1, Folder 17)
    - Margaret Folly (Carton 1, Folder 18)
    - Jeanne E. Francoeur, 1915 (Carton 1, Folder 19)
    - Margaret Ladd Franklin, 1913 (Carton 1, Folder 20)
    - John Palmer Gavit, 1937 (Carton 1, Folder 21)
    - Henry George (Carton 1, Folder 22)
    - W.E. Goschen, 1914 (Carton 1, Folder 23)
    - Lynn Haines with Henry Raymond Mussey, 1920 (Carton 1, Folder 24)
    - Ida Husted Harper, 1906-1911 (Carton 1, Folder 25)
    - J. Thomas Heflin, 1914 (Carton 1, Folder 26)
    - Clayton Herrington, 1914 (Carton 1, Folder 27)
    - George N. Hodgdon (Carton 1, Folder 28)
    - Frederic C. Howe (Carton 1, Folder 29)
    - Julia Ward Howe, 1909 (Carton 1, Folder 30)
    - Austin E. Hutcheson, 1948 (Carton 1, Folder 31)
    - Ernst Jackh, 1927 (Carton 1, Folder 32)
    - Otto H. Kahn, 1918 (Carton 1, Folder 33)
    - Frederick M. Kerby (Carton 1, Folder 34)
    - Frederick J. Libby, 1934 (Carton 1, Folder 35)
    - Lola Maverick Lloyd, 1918 (Carton 1, Folder 36)
    - E.N. Martin, 1946 (Carton 1, Folder 37)
    - Pat McCarran, 1950 (Carton 1, Folder 38)
    - H.S. McCluskey (Carton 1, Folder 39)
    - Catherine Waugh McCulloch, 1909-1912 (Carton 1, Folder 40)
    - Elmwood Mead, 1918 (Carton 1, Folder 41)
    - John Stuart Mill, 1867 (Carton 1, Folder 42)
    - A. Grant Miller, 1920 (Carton 1, Folder 43)
    - Raymond B. Morgan, 1915 (Carton 1, Folder 44)
    - Clelia Duel Mosher, 1921 (Carton 1, Folder 45)
    - Harold Owen, 1912 (Carton 1, Folder 46)
    - Adella M. Parker (Carton 1, Folder 47)
    - Raymond V. Phelan (Carton 1, Folder 48)
    - Miles Poindexter, 1920 (Carton 1, Folder 49)
    - Frances Squire Potter (Carton 1, Folder 50)
    - Rachel A. Rees, 1920 (Carton 1, Folder 51)
    - Edith Robert-Tornow, 1911 (Carton 1, Folder 52)
    - Margaret Hayden Rorke, 1914 (Carton 1, Folder 53)
    - Nathaniel Schmidt, 1909 (Carton 1, Folder 54)
    - John F. Shafroth, 1910 (Carton 1, Folder 55)
    - Mrs. Phillip Snowden, 1909 (Carton 1, Folder 56)
    - W.I. Thomas (Carton 1, Folder 57)
    - Charles A. Towne, 1916 (Carton 1, Folder 58)
    - Edwin B. Van Aken, 1918 (Carton 1, Folder 59)
    - Bulkeley Wells, Jr. (Carton 1, Folder 60)
    - Francis Ralston Welsh (Carton 1, Folder 61)
    - Harry H. Willock (Carton 1, Folder 62)
    - B.M. Wilson (Carton 1, Folder 63)
    - Mary Young (Mrs. John Craig) (Carton 1, Folder 64)
    - Anonymous, 1886-1941 (Carton 1, Folder 65)
  - Bibliographic Research Notes (Carton 1, Folder 66-68)
  - Biographical sketches (Carton 1, Folder 69)
  - Business cards (Carton 1, Folder 70)
  - Calling cards (Carton 1, Folder 71)
  - Campaign Files, 1912-1924
    - Agenda, circa 1920 (Carton 1, Folder 72-73)
    - Anne Martin Club Members, 1918 (Carton 1, Folder 74)
    - sample ballot (Carton 1, Folder 75)
    - Committee rosters, 1917-1920 (Carton 1, Folder 76)
    - Contacts (Carton 1, Folder 77-79)
    - Contributions, 1917-1920 (Carton 1, Folder 80)
    - Cox-Roosevelt Campaign, 1919-1920 (Carton 1, Folder 81)
    - Endorsements, circa 1920 (Carton 1, Folder 82)
    - Event Announcements, 1918-1920 (Carton 1, Folder 83)
    - Expenditures, 1918-1920 (Carton 1, Folder 84-85)
    - Form Letters, 1918-1920 (Carton 1, Folder 86)
    - Handbills (Carton 1, Folder 87)
    - Charles B. Henderson, 1918 (Carton 1, Folder 88)
    - Hughes Campaign Service, 1916 (Carton 2, Folder 1)
    - Instructions for Organizers, circa 1920 (Carton 2, Folder 2)
    - Itinerary (Carton 2, Folder 3)
    - Job Advertisements, 1920 (Carton 2, Folder 4)
    - La Follette-Wheeler Progressive, 1924 (Carton 2, Folder 5)
    - W.T. McNeil, 1920 (Carton 2, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Advertising Rates, 1918 (Carton 2, Folder 7)
    - Official Returns, 1914-1924 (Carton 2, Folder 8)
    - Opponents (Carton 2, Folder 9)
    - Petitions for Nomination, 1918-1920 (Carton 2, Folder 10-15)
    - Key Pittman (Carton 2, Folder 16)
    - Platforms, 1918 (Carton 2, Folder 17)
    - Press List (Carton 2, Folder 18)
    - Press Releases, 1918-1920 (Carton 2, Folder 19-21)
    - Profiteering and the Railroads, 1916 (Carton 2, Folder 22)
    - Registered Voters, 1912-1918 (Carton 2, Folder 23-30)
    - Speeches (Carton 2, Folder 31)
    - Tax Lists, 1913-1918 (Carton 2, Folder 32)
    - Voting Polls, 1918 (Carton 2, Folder 33)
  - Contacts, 1914-1921 (Carton 2, Folder 34-35)
  - Correspondence- drafts, 1913-1951 (Carton 2, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence- drafts, 1913-1951 (Carton 3, Folder 1)
  - Event Programs, 1913-1950 (Carton 3, Folder 2)
  - Finance and Business Notes, circa 1916 (Carton 3, Folder 3)
  - List of Leaflets (Carton 3, Folder 34)
  - Meeting Notes (Carton 3, Folder 35)
  - Memos (Carton 3, Folder 36)
  - Petitions, 1939-1942 (Carton 7, Folder 56)
  - Legislative, 1867-1950
    - California Irrigation Laws (Carton 3, Folder 4)
    - Committee on the Judiciary Statement of Mrs. Carrie Chapman Catt, 1904 (Carton 3, Folder 5)
    - Committee on the Public Lands Opinion of the Supreme Court, 1914-1916 (Carton 3, Folder 6)
    - Constitution of Nevada, 1912 (Carton 3, Folder 7)
    - Department of Agriculture, 1918 (Carton 3, Folder 8)
    - Department of Civil Service Reform (Carton 3, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior, Land Office, 1916-1917 (Carton 3, Folder 10)
    - Department of Social Welfare, 1937 (Carton 3, Folder 11)
    - Digest of Laws Regarding Representation of a New Party (Carton 3, Folder 12)
    - Draft Acts, 1913-1949 (Carton 3, Folder 13)
    - Extracts from Governor's Message to Legislature, 1913-1917 (Carton 3, Folder 14)
    - Herbert Hoover's Statement, 1941 (Carton 3, Folder 15)
    - House of Representatives, 1913-1917 (Carton 3, Folder 16)
    - Gerrit J. Johnson on single tax, 1918 (Carton 3, Folder 17)
    - Hearing...regarding the use of Lake Tahoe, 1919 (Carton 3, Folder 18)
    - Laws of Nevada 27th Session, 1915 (Carton 3, Folder 19)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1867 (Carton 3, Folder 20)
    - Official List of Members of the House of Representatives, 1917 (Carton 3, Folder 21)
    - Opinion of the Supreme Court re: Presidential Pardons (Carton 3, Folder 22)
    - Peace Bill, 1940-1941 (Carton 3, Folder 23)
    - Penal System, 1920 (Carton 3, Folder 24)
    - Personnel of the Nevada State Legislature, 1919 (Carton 3, Folder 25)
    - Presidential Addresses, 1914-1917 (Carton 3, Folder 26-27)
    - Primary Elections Law, 1909 (Carton 3, Folder 28)
    - Proposed Retail Liquor Ordinance, 1915 (Carton 3, Folder 29)
    - Senate Bills, 1916-1945 (Carton 3, Folder 30)
    - Venereal Disease Prevention Law, 1948 (Carton 3, Folder 31)
    - War Congress, 1918 (Carton 3, Folder 32)
    - Woman Suffrage, 1915 (Carton 3, Folder 33)
  - Photographs and Drawings, 1891-1918 (Carton 7, Folder 57)
  - Protest, circa 1918 (Carton 7, Folder 58)
  - Publication Announcements (Carton 7, Folder 59)
  - Songs, 1911-1912 (Carton 8, Folder 8)
  - Subscriptions, 1914-1920 (Carton 8, Folder 9)
  - Telegrams [drafts], 1916-1935 (Carton 8, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1914-1950
    - Mary Austin, 1914-1920 (Carton 3, Folder 37)
    - Anne Martin, 1911-1950 (Carton 3, Folder 38-41)
    - Peace and Conflict, 1928-1948 (Carton 3, Folder 42-45)
    - Politics, 1916-1949 (Carton 4, Folder 1-4)
    - Riots and Protests, 1910-1921 (Carton 4, Folder 5)
    - Social Welfare Politics, 1914-1950 (Carton 4, Folder 6-10)
    - Woman's Suffrage, 1914-1947 (Carton 4, Folder 11-16)
    - Miscellany, 1911-1950 (Carton 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Organizations, 1904-1949
    - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1918 (Carton 4, Folder 19)
    - All American Farm Labor Cooperation Commission (Carton 4, Folder 20)
    - American Association for Agricultural Legislation, 1918 (Carton 4, Folder 21)
    - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1916-1918 (Carton 4, Folder 22)
    - American Association of University Women, 1946 (Carton 4, Folder 23)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 1)
    - American Committee for Fairplay in China, 1928 (Carton 5, Folder 2)
    - American Defense Society, 1918 (Carton 5, Folder 3)
    - American Labor Party of Greater New York, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 4)
    - American Legion Auxiliary, 1948 (Carton 5, Folder 5)
    - American Proportional Representation League, 1916-1918 (Carton 5, Folder 6)
    - American Social Hygiene Association, 1949 (Carton 5, Folder 7)
    - American Women's Club, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 8)
    - Anti-Saloon League of Nevada, 1918 (Carton 5, Folder 9)
    - Arizona Colorado River Development Association, 1927 (Carton 5, Folder 10)
    - Business Men's Association of Washoe (Carton 5, Folder 11)
    - California Civic League, 1912 (Carton 5, Folder 12)
    - California Equal Suffrage Association, circa 1911 (Carton 5, Folder 13)
    - California Federation of Labor, 1918 (Carton 5, Folder 14)
    - California League of Women Voters, 1942 (Carton 5, Folder 15)
    - Campaign for World Government (Carton 5, Folder 16)
    - Carmel Art Association (Carton 5, Folder 17)
    - Central Labor Council of Portland (Carton 5, Folder 18)
    - Citizen's Amnesty Committee, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 19)
    - College Equal Suffrage League, 1911 (Carton 5, Folder 20)
    - College Equal Suffrage League of Northern California (Carton 5, Folder 21)
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, 1941 (Carton 5, Folder 22)
    - Committee of '48, 1919-1920 (Carton 5, Folder 23)
    - Committee of One-Hundred on Ireland, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Coal Mine Managers, 1914 (Carton 5, Folder 25)
    - Committee on Women's Suffrage, 1913 (Carton 5, Folder 26)
    - Committee on World Friendship Among Children (Carton 5, Folder 27)
    - Committee to Defend America by Waging Peace (Carton 5, Folder 28)
    - Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage, 1913-1916 (Carton 5, Folder 29)
    - Connecticut Woman Suffrage Association, circa 1914 (Carton 5, Folder 30)
    - Constitutional Society for Women's Suffrage (Carton 5, Folder 31)
    - County Equal Suffrage Association (Carton 5, Folder 32)
    - Delaware Campaign Committee for Woman Suffrage, 1915 (Carton 5, Folder 33)
    - Democratic National Committee (Carton 5, Folder 34)
    - Department of Labor Children's Bureau, 1918 (Carton 5, Folder 35)
    - Educational Directory, 1912 (Carton 5, Folder 36)
    - Equal Rights in Industry, Business, the Professions and Politics, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 37)
    - Equal Suffrage Association for Good Government (Carton 5, Folder 38)
    - Equal Suffrage Association of Minnesota (Carton 5, Folder 39)
    - Equal Suffrage Club of Berkeley, California, 1911 (Carton 5, Folder 40)
    - Equal Suffrage League of Morgan County West Virginia, 1916 (Carton 5, Folder 41)
    - Dr. Equi Defense Committee (Carton 5, Folder 42)
    - Fabian Women's Group, 1909 (Carton 5, Folder 43)
    - Farm Labor Party, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 44)
    - Federal Suffrage Association, 1914 (Carton 5, Folder 45)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Carton 5, Folder 46)
    - Headquarters Against Dry Initiative (Carton 5, Folder 47)
    - Hindustan Gadar Party (Carton 5, Folder 48)
    - Hull House, 1925-1937 (Carton 5, Folder 49)
    - Henry E. Huntington Library, 1948 (Carton 5, Folder 50)
    - Illinois Equal Suffrage Association, 1914 (Carton 5, Folder 51)
    - Indiana Equal Suffrage Association, 1915 (Carton 5, Folder 52)
    - Indiana Republican State Committee (Carton 5, Folder 53)
    - Institute of International Relations, 1939 (Carton 5, Folder 54)
    - International Free Trade League, 1918 (Carton 5, Folder 55)
    - International Woman's Suffrage Alliance, 1906-1913 (Carton 5, Folder 56-57)
    - Irish Women Worker's Union (Carton 5, Folder 58)
    - Keep America Out of War Congress, 1941 (Carton 5, Folder 59)
    - K-H Newsletter, London, England, 1939 (Carton 5, Folder 60)
    - League of Nations, 1930-1935 (Carton 5, Folder 61)
    - League of Self Supporting Women (Carton 5, Folder 62)
    - League to Enforce Peace, 1918 (Carton 5, Folder 63)
    - Liberty Labor League, 1918 (Carton 5, Folder 64)
    - Massachusetts Men's Association Opposed to the Further Extension of Suffrage to Women, 1913 (Carton 5, Folder 65)
    - Massachusetts Civic Alliance, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 66)
    - Massachusetts Woman's Suffrage Association (Carton 5, Folder 67)
    - Men's Equal Franchise Society of the University of Nevada, 1914 (Carton 5, Folder 68)
    - Men's League for Woman Suffrage, 1911-1914 (Carton 5, Folder 69)
    - Montana Equal Suffrage State Central Committee (Carton 5, Folder 70)
    - Montana Good Government Organization (Carton 5, Folder 71)
    - National American Woman's Suffrage Association, 1904-1916 (Carton 5, Folder 72-75)
    - National Arts Club, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 76)
    - National Association Opposed to Woman Suffrage, 1912-1916 (Carton 5, Folder 77)
    - National Brewer's Association, 1913 (Carton 5, Folder 78)
    - National Committee for Prevention of War, 1927-1941 (Carton 5, Folder 79)
    - National Consumer's League, circa 1914 (Carton 5, Folder 80)
    - National Council for Prevention of War, 1927-1944 (Carton 5, Folder 81)
    - National Council of Women Voters, 1911-1915 (Carton 5, Folder 82)
    - National Dry Federation (Carton 5, Folder 83)
    - National Enfranchisement of Women (Carton 5, Folder 84)
    - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 85)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1920-1941 (Carton 5, Folder 86)
    - National League for Opposing Woman Suffrage (Carton 5, Folder 87)
    - National League of Women Voters, 1939 (Carton 5, Folder 88)
    - National Popular Government League, 1920 (Carton 5, Folder 89)
    - National Security League, 1918 (Carton 5, Folder 90)
    - National Society of the Daughters of the American Revolution, 1945 (Carton 5, Folder 91)
    - National Women's Christian Temperance Union (Carton 5, Folder 92)
    - National Woman's Party, circa 1945 (Carton 6, Folder 1-7)
    - National Woman Suffrage Headquarters, 1906 (Carton 6, Folder 8)
    - National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co. Inc., 1915 (Carton 6, Folder 9)
    - Nevada Association of Women Opposed to Equal Suffrage, 1914 (Carton 6, Folder 10)
    - Nevada Business Women, 1948 (Carton 6, Folder 11)
    - Nevada Equal Franchise Society, 1910-1920 (Carton 6, Folder 12-30)
    - Nevada Women's Civic League, circa 1916 (Carton 6, Folder 31)
    - New Jersey Women's Suffrage Association, 1915 (Carton 6, Folder 32)
    - New York State Association Opposed to Woman Suffrage (Carton 6, Folder 33)
    - New York State Woman's Suffrage Association, 1909 (Carton 6, Folder 34)
    - Non-Partisan League Headquarters (Carton 6, Folder 35)
    - Oklahoma Woman Suffrage Association, 1909 (Carton 6, Folder 36)
    - Open Door Council (Carton 6, Folder 37)
    - Pacific Co-operative League (Carton 6, Folder 38)
    - Pacifist Action Committee, 1930 (Carton 6, Folder 39)
    - Pan Pacific Union, 1928 (Carton 6, Folder 40)
    - Pan Pacific Women's Conference, 1928 (Carton 6, Folder 41)
    - Partito Per Il Suffragio alla Donna (Carton 6, Folder 42)
    - People's Mandate to Government to End War, circa 1945 (Carton 6, Folder 43)
    - Political Equality League (Carton 7, Folder 1)
    - Political Equality League of Wisconsin- Press Bulletin, 1912 (Carton 7, Folder 2)
    - Portland Woman's Club (Carton 7, Folder 3)
    - Post War World Council, 1943 (Carton 7, Folder 4)
    - Prohibition National Committee (Carton 7, Folder 5)